http://www.spamarrest.com/privacy/

To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that
Spam Arrest LLC ("Spam Arrest") is
committed to protecting your privacy. We have made a commitment to maintain
strict requirements regarding how we treat your information.
The information on this Web site (the
"Site") is being offered by Spam Arrest LLC ("Spam Arrest"). If you use Spam
Arrest's free e-mail service, please refer the privacy policy set forth
here. This privacy statement is designed to tell you how
we collect and use personal information so you can make an informed decision
about using our Site. Please read this statement before using our Site or
submitting any personal information to us. By using our Site, you consent to the
information collection and use practices described herein.
CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT
If we decide to change our privacy
policy or our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy
statement, our home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are
aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what
circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this
privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make
material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means
of a notice on our home page.
Your use of the Site following the
posting of such changes or revised statement shall constitute your acceptance of
any such changes. We encourage you to review our privacy statement whenever you
visit our Site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you
provide will be used. This privacy statement applies to all users of this Site,
including but not limited to Spam Arrest's customers who register for our
services ("Customers") and to persons or entities that send email to Customers
("Senders"). This privacy statement applies only to our online information
collection and use practices through this Web site and does not apply to Spam
Arrest's offline information collection and use practices.
SPECIAL NOTICES:
1. Spam Arrest employees do not access
the content of any emails filtered through Spam Arrest services unless you
specifically request them to do so (for example, if you are having technical
difficulties accessing your account) or if required by law, to maintain our
system, or to protect Spam Arrest or the public.
2. No human reads your email to target
content or related information to you without your consent.
3. We will not sell, share, or rent any
personal information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this
statement without first obtaining your authorization.
4. We never share your personally identifying information with any
advertiser as part of this service, unless you specifically ask us to do so.
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT
Although the majority of information
obtained through this Site is business related, we may also collect personal
information (i.e., individual information that may be used to personally
identify or contact you) from Customers, Senders, and other users of this Site.
Collection is done both actively (information you voluntarily submit to us) and
passively (information automatically gathered from your computer).
ACTIVE COLLECTION. At several places on our Site, we collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us that may contain personally identifiable information. For Customers, for example, our registration page requests your full name, address, phone number, fax
number, email address, email server host name and email user name and password. If you do not provide such information you may not be able to use the Site and service offered therein. When importing your email address book or adding email addresses as a contact to the
site, these addresses will be used to pre-authorize communications with these users.
For Senders, our identity verification page requests your full name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, and email name. You may also
provide us with credit card information for payment of registration fees or other fees collected by Spam Arrest. If you send us an email request, we may also store that information. Spam Arrest also will store emails sent to Customers from Senders for an indefinite
period of time, as back-up copies for the purposes of recovery from errors or system failure.
PASSIVE COLLECTION. Our software
automatically collects certain information from your computer (such as your
Internet address, browser type, operating software, computer language, email
type, etc.) using three methods: (1) cookies, (2) log files, and (3) a
software download.
1. Cookies. A cookie is a piece of data
stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of
a cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information while on our
Site. We use cookies to track a user's path for security purposes, as well as to
target their interests in an effort to enhance the experience on our Site. If
you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser
instructions or help screen to learn about these functions. If a user rejects a
cookie, they may still use our Site: however, they will be limited in some of
its areas. For example, the user may not receive promotions or product
information. Spam Arrest reserves the right to prohibit access to and use of the
Site if cookies are disabled. Please note: While some of our business partners
may use cookies on our Site, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
2. Log Files. We use IP addresses to
analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement, and gather broad
demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to
personally identifiable information.
3. Software Download. When a Customer
initially registers with Spam Arrest, he or she will be required to download
software to his or her computer in order to complete registration. This software
will gather information regarding the Customer's computer such as the type of
operating software, the computer language, the type of email (e.g., Outlook,
Netscape). This software also will gather other information regarding the
Customer including the user's name and password, email host server, and IP
address. The information collected is used internally by Spam Arrest to
facilitate provision of unwanted email ("spam") blocking services to Customers.
Such information (but not user and password information) may be sold or provided
to third parties in aggregate form.
Aside from the methods listed above, we do not use any tracking technologies in
conjunction with your email. For example, when you send an email, we do not use
cookies to monitor whether the recipient has received it.
E-MAIL SERVER CONTENTS
The content within (a) your Spam Arrest
e-mail service account and (b) the e-mail server you designate during the E-mail
Service registration process, are retrieved, stored and maintained on Spam
Arrest's servers in order to provide Spam Arrest services to you. Because we
keep back-up copies of data for the purposes of recovery from errors or system
failure, residual copies of email may remain on our systems for some time, even
after you have deleted messages from your mailbox or after the termination of
your account.
HOW DO WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?
Spam Arrest is the sole owner of the
information collected on this Site. Personal information that you provide Spam
Arrest (such as a personal email address) may be used by Spam Arrest in the
following ways:
* to contact you about your use of the
Site or about our products and services;
* to respond to your comments or
requests;
* to maintain a record of the
relationship between email addresses to provide the spam blocking services;
* to request feedback and to enable us
to develop and improve the Site and our products and services;
* for internal and Spam Arrest
marketing/promotional purposes including newsletters (you can opt out of
receiving marketing/promotional materials by completing the Termination of
Service form on the Site); and
* for the specific purpose for which the
information was provided and to otherwise provide the spam blocking services
described in the Spam Arrest Terms of Service Agreement.
For example, we send new Customers and
other users a welcoming email to verify password and username, and established
Customers will occasionally receive information on product services or special
promotions. Customers must accept such commercial/promotional emails as a
requirement of our service. Please see "What Choices Do You Have Regarding The
Use Of Your Information?" below regarding your options not to receive such
communications. We also send Customers Site and service announcement updates via
email. Receiving such email announcements is a condition of our service, as they
contain important information about our service. If you do not wish to receive
them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You may do that by
completing the Termination of Service form on the Site.
For Senders, your information will be
used to confirm or re-confirm your identity as a party authorized to send email
to a particular Customer or Customers, to develop and maintain "scoring"
information attributable to a particular Sender's email address, and to provide
the spam blocking services described in the Spam Arrest Terms of Service
Agreement. Your email address will not be used for marketing purposes, sold or
shared with third parties, unless required by law.
For Spammers, your information may be
sold or otherwise provided to spam monitoring, compliance, government and
non-government organizations.
Except as set forth herein, Spam Arrest will not disclose Customer email
addresses, or the email addresses of Senders, to any third parties, including,
but not limited to, direct marketers.
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES?
We will not sell, share, or rent any personal information or email address to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement without first obtaining your authorization. We may provide aggregate information (i.e., information we collect that does not allow you to be personally identified or contacted) to third parties without your authorization, such as information about your access and use of the Site, about your computer operating system and computer language, email type, and similar information.
We may disclose personal information you
provide to independent contractors, service providers and consultants who are
engaged by or working with Spam Arrest. For example, we may use credit card
processing companies to process payments for goods and services, outside
shipping companies to ship orders and credit bureaus to check credit histories.
We may partner with other parties to provide specific services and will share
information with them in order to facilitate their provision of services. For
example, when the Customer, Sender, or other user signs up for these services,
we will share names, or other contact information necessary for the third party
to provide these services.
We may also disclose personal
information we have collected if we are required to do so by law or if, in our
good faith judgment, such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal
process, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights of Spam Arrest and
its customers and the public.
Please note: This Site may contain links
to other sites. Please be aware that Spam Arrest is not responsible for the
privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our Customers, Senders, or
other users of the Site to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the
privacy statements of every Web site that collects personally identifiable
information. Similarly, if you entered the Site through another Web site, Spam
Arrest is also not responsible for the privacy practices of that site, and you
should review the privacy policy of the originating Web site before providing
any personal information to that Web site. This privacy statement applies solely
to information collected by Spam Arrest.
WHAT STEPS DO WE TAKE TO PROTECT YOUR
INFORMATION?
Spam Arrest understands that security of
your information and your email address is vital to your business. Spam Arrest
provides four levels of protection against unauthorized access to your
information: (1) global security using SSL encryption technology, (2) firewall
security for protection of our Web and database servers against external attack,
(3) encrypted password protection for your account.
HOW CAN YOU CORRECT AND UPDATE YOUR
PERSONAL INFORMATION?
If you wish to correct your email
address or any personally identifiable information (such as zip code, phone
number, etc.), please contact us at the address or email indicated below and we
will endeavor to correct or update the personal data you have provided us to the
extent such information is not necessary to complete any services or
transactions with us.
CHOICE / OPT-OUT
We provide you the opportunity to "opt
out" of our use of your personally identifiable information. If you no longer
wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, and also wish to
withdraw permission for us to use your personally identifiable information, you
may opt-out by canceling your services with Spam Arrest. You may cancel your
services by completing the Termination of Service form on the Site.
You will be notified when your personal
information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service
provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your
information with that party.
Please note that for users of our
services who do not become Customers following the thirty (30) day free trial
period, we will continue to monitor and track email sent to such user unless and
until the user completes the Termination of Service form on the Site or Spam
Arrest decides to cease monitoring and tracking emails sent to such user.
If you feel that Spam Arrest is not abiding by this privacy statement, you
should contact our Privacy Compliance Coordinator by email at privacy@spamarrest.com
or by mail at 7683 SE 27th Street, PMB 273, Mercer Island WA 98040.
As seen and heard on
30 day Free Trial
AffiliatesAppsCompanyContactEnterprisePartnersNews/PressPrivacyTerms
©2016 Spam Arrest, LLC. All Rights Reserved. US Patent #7,039,949/R E 40, 992
